wearticles.com 2016-06-25

# WEARTICLES

Privacy Policy

WeArticles.com® – PRIVACY POLICY  
[Effective as of November 1st, 2013]  
Address: WeArticles®, Los Angeles, CA 90046.  
WeArticles® (“WeArticles,”  
WeArticles.COM,” ) is deeply committed to respecting and protecting  
the privacy and security rights of users and the information you share with us at the WeArticles website  
(the “Website”). WeArticles created this Privacy Policy to give you (“You” or “Your”) assurance of  
WeArticles’s commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of Your privacy as You  
visit and use the Website (the “Privacy Policy”).  
We believe YOU have the right to know everything regarding the information we collect about  
YOU, how this information benefits You, and how you can say “no” to the use of any of this  
information. This Privacy Policy explains what we do with your information and what You can  
expect from WeArticles. By using the Website, You indicate your acceptance of WeArticles’s Privacy Policy.  
WeArticles’s data collection and retention practices are designed to provide transparency,  
accountability and choice regarding the management and use of Your personal information  
(“Personal Information”). If You have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy  
or practices, please contact us at via e-mail at " admin@WeArticles.com. This Privacy  
Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any websites of third-parties (“Third-Party  
Websites”), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ  
materially from this Privacy Policy. You should consult privacy policies for all other sites, as  
WeArticles has no control over information submitted to or collected by such third-parties.  
You may visit WeArticles at any time without providing Your identity or revealing any personal  
information about yourself. However, when You visit our Website, we may collect and store  
Your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from WeArticles,  
ad data, IP address and standard web log information, and information from other companies,  
such as demographic and navigation data. In order to be approved as registered user with WeArticles,  
You will be required to choose a user-name. This user-name may be displayed throughout WeArticles  
and therefore provided to the public. Unless You associate your user-name with Your Personal  
Information, users will not be able to personally identify Your activities on WeArticles.  
When visiting WeArticles from a public or shared computer, certain information about You, such as  
Your user-name, may also be visible to others who may use the computer after Your use.  
BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE  
READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY  
POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY  
THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.  
WeArticles has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices  
have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s program requirements:(http:/  
 "http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-" www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy- programs-  
requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection  
and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that  
may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third  
party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its  
leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints  
regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [PUT SOMETHING ERE:  
COMPANY CONTACT INFO]. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact  
TRUSTe at   "http://www.watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint" http://www.watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint.  
1\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY  
We care about the safety of children. WeArticles does not solicit or knowingly collect Personal  
Information from children under the age of 13. Children should always get permission from  
their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as, their names, e-  
mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet to us or to anyone else. We encourage  
You to become involved in Your children’s on-line experience and to share Your interest in our  
Website with Your young ones. If WeArticles obtains actual knowledge that it has collected Personal  
Information from a child under the age of 13, WeArticles will immediately delete such information  
from its database.  
2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES  
WeArticles collects Personal Information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information  
to us on the Website and through e-mail. When visiting the Website, we collect user-specific  
information on what pages are visited.  
Personal Information  
When You register for our service, You will be asked to provide WeArticles certain Personal  
Information. Personal Information includes, without limitation: Your first name, last  
name, user-name, password, e-mail address, gender, date of birth, city, state, and zip  
code. The Website will not gather Personal Information surreptitiously.  
In general, once You provide us with Your required Personal Information, You are no  
longer anonymous. In providing us with Your Personal Information, You consent to  
the transfer and storage of such information on our servers. In addition to the foregoing  
Personal Information in connection with your registration and use of WeArticles, we may  
collect and store the following Personal Information:  
• all transactional information based on your activities on WeArticles;  
• any correspondence sent to us; and  
• other supplemental information from third-parties.  
Our primary purpose in collecting Personal Information is to provide You with a safe,  
smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use Your Personal  
Information to:  
provide the services and customer support You request;  
resolve disputes;  
troubleshoot problems;  
prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;  
enforce our Terms and Conditions;  
customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; and  
inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and  
promotional offers.  
Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect Your privacy and our ability to  
keep the community free from bad actors, WeArticles will maintain an e-mail database,  
in-house, and will never sell Your data, to include postal and/or e-mail address(es).  
Further, we will not otherwise disclose Your Personal Information to law enforcement,  
other government officials, or other third-parties without a subpoena, court order or  
substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the  
disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial  
loss or to report suspected illegal activity.  
Traffic Data  
Like most website operators, WeArticles automatically gathers information of the sort that  
browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers;  
(iii) types of computers accessing the Website; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing  
the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that  
does not personally identify You.  
Cookies  
WeArticles uses so-called “Cookies,” which are files that are stored on Your computer that  
can be retrieved to assist in customizing Your experience with the online service.  
A “Cookie” is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and  
that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the  
website. The purpose of a “Cookie” is to (1) support the functionality of the Website,  
for example by keeping track of Your visual preferences or controlling the frequency  
of “WeArticles-up” windows, and (2) identify the user as a unique user of the Website.  
WeArticles uses “Cookies” to customize Your experience on the Website to Your interests, to  
ensure that You do not repeatedly see content or informational messages that may be of  
no interest to You, and to store Your password so You do not have to re-enter it each  
time You visit the Website.  
If You want to disable “Cookies,” there is a simple procedure in most Internet browsers  
that allows You to turn-off “Cookies.” Please remember, however, that “Cookies” may  
be required to allow You to use certain features of the Website.  
For additional information on WeArticles’s uses of “Cookies,” see the section concerning  
Information Use and Disclosure Practices, below.  
IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE “COOKIES” PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER,  
YOU SHOULD ADJUST THE CORRESPONDING SETTING IN YOUR BROWSER  
TO REFUSE “COOKIES” BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE  
UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN  
FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT  
THE AID OF “COOKIES.” IF YOU REFUSE “COOKIES,” YOU ASSUME ALL  
RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.  
Web Beacons/Web Bugs  
WeArticles utilizes a software technology called “clear gifs” (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs),  
that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  
Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to “Cookies,” and  
are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to “Cookies,” which  
are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web  
pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the  
information gathered by clear gifs to our customer’s Personal Information. Rather, we  
use clear gifs in our HTML-based e-mails to let us know which e-mails have been opened  
by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and  
the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  
Some of our Third-Party Websites (e.g., Third-Party Advertising Promotions) use “Cookies” and  
Web Beacons on the Website. We have no access to or control over these third-party tracking  
technologies.  
You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to  
do so may prevent You from using certain of the Services.  
3\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES  
(a) Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using “Cookies”  
WeArticles analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using “Cookies” to help WeArticles better  
understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and  
trends in usage, WeArticles is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to  
serve You more relevant and interesting content and third-party advertising promotions. From  
time to time, WeArticles may release Traffic Data and information gathered using “Cookies” in the  
aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. WeArticles does not  
attempt to link information gathered using “Cookies” to Personal Information.  
(b) Personal Information  
Generally, WeArticles uses Your Personal Information to send You information about WeArticles and WeArticles’s-  
products and services, and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Services.  
WeArticles uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Website.  
Except under the following circumstances, WeArticles will keep Your Personal Information private,  
and will not share it with third-parties.  
Third-Party Marketing: By submitting Your Personal Information  
to us and opting-in, You grant us the right, subject to applicable  
state and federal law, to use that Personal Information for marketing  
purposes. We may rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all  
Personal Information with or to any third-party for any and all uses  
permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. These third-  
parties may include: (a) providers of the products and/or service that  
you requested and/or won by and through our Website; (b) providers  
of direct marketing services and applications; (c) e-mail marketers;  
(d) telemarketers; and (e) direct marketers; and  
WeArticles discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide services,  
including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing  
tasks such as hosting, fulfillment, and data storage and security. These  
service providers are prohibited from using this Personal Information for  
any other purpose including their own marketing purposes; and  
WeArticles discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in  
response to a subpoena or court order, or when WeArticles believes in its sole  
discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or  
rights of WeArticles, third-parties, or the public at large; and  
WeArticles reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its  
possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger,  
acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of WeArticles’s assets.  
Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use  
and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to  
this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice  
of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of  
it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however,  
may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by a WeArticles successor  
organization.  
(c) Opting-In  
WeArticles does not share Personal Information with anyone, unless You “opt in” to having Your  
information shared with third-parties, or we have informed You of a change to our Privacy  
Policy so that You can then choose to opt-out. It’s that simple.  
If you have opted-in to receiving information from third-parties, we will provide You with a way  
to tell us that You no longer want us to share Personal Information and that You no longer want  
to receive promotional and/or marketing information about products, services, and offerings  
from any third-parties. We will also provide You with a way to update the Personal Information  
that You share with us during registration. Once You have “opted-in” and agreed that Your  
information may be shared with third-parties or You have responded directly to an offer by  
any third-party on the WeArticles Website, WeArticles will not be able to update any of Your Personal  
Information that has been transferred to such third-parties or opt You out of such third-parties  
so that You no longer receive their promotional and/or marketing information. Instead, You  
must either contact that third-party or refer to their individual privacy policy to update Your  
Personal Information, or to let them know that You no longer want to receive promotional and/or  
marketing information about their products, services, or offerings.  
4\. CONSENT TO RECEIVE E-MAIL FROM WeArticles  
By establishing an account with WeArticles, You consent to receive periodic commercial/promotional  
e-mail communications from WeArticles concerning WeArticles – products and services. You may opt-out  
of receiving such communications at any time by (a) following the unsubscribe instructions  
contained in each e-mail; (b) sending an e-mail to   " admin@WeArticles.com; (c)  
writing to us at :  Los Angeles, CA 90046.  
5\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
WeArticles has implemented and maintains generally accepted industry standards to protect against the  
unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information  
both during transmission and once we receive it. The security of Your personal information  
is important to us. When you enter sensitive information during the registration process, we  
encrypt that information using state-of-the-art technology.  
However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100%  
secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your  
personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
WeArticles assures you that we will use Your e-mail address, with Your express consent, only for the  
purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not otherwise rent or sell Your e-mail address  
to third-parties, and we will prevent Your e-mail address from being recorded by “web  
crawlers” or “web spiders” to the best of our ability. If You believe that your e-mail address  
has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.  
If You have any questions about security on our Website, You can e-mail us at  
 "mail to: admin@WeArticles.com."  
6\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES  
The Website includes links to other Third-Party Websites whose privacy practices may differ  
from those of WeArticles. If You submit Personal Information to any of a Third-Party Website, your  
Personal Information is governed by their privacy statements. WeArticles encourages You to carefully  
read the privacy statement of any Third-Party Website You visit.  
7\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION  
WeArticles wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. By using the Website, You  
represent and warrant that all information You provide on any registration form or otherwise  
in connection with Your use of the Website and Services will be complete and accurate, and  
that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy.  
To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, Your Personal  
Information, please email us at   "mail to:" admin@WeArticles.com.  
8\. PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES  
From time to time, WeArticles may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions  
(collectively, “Promotional Activities”). Any information submitted in connection with  
Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time,  
WeArticles may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help WeArticles improve the Website or  
services. Any Personal Information provided to WeArticles in connection with any survey will be  
used only in relation to that survey, and may be disclosed to third-parties not bound by this  
Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.  
9\. RULES FOR SUBMISSIONS AND MESSAGES IN CHAT ROOMS  
If You use a bulletin board or chat room on the Website, You should be aware that any Personal  
Information that You submit there can be read, collected and/or used by other users of those  
forums, and could be used to send You unsolicited messages. Responsibility for what is posted  
in the discussion groups or other public forums lies with each user – You alone are responsible  
for the content of Your messages and the consequences of any such messages. We cannot and do  
not review every submission a user may make. We neither endorse nor guarantee the accuracy or  
propriety of any submission. We do, however, reserve the right but do not assume the obligation  
to restrict or prohibit Your use of our Website if we believe you are violating any of the terms of  
the agreement and to remove, edit, or relocate any submission as we see fit whether for legal or  
other reasons.  
We are not responsible for the Personal Information that You choose to submit in the Website  
forums. We reserve the right to terminate the member status of anyone who uses the forums in a  
manner inconsistent with our Terms of Service.  
10\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the  
home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we  
collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right  
to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material  
changes to this policy, we will notify You here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our home  
page within thirty (30) days of such changes being made.  
11\. REVOKING CONSENT/DELETING YOUR ACCOUNT  
You can delete or deactivate your WeArticles account at any time by e-mailing  
" admin@WeArticles.com. When You delete your account, Your Personal Information  
is removed from our database, unless we are required to save the data by applicable law, to  
prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, and/or enforce  
our General Terms of Use. As a rule it takes two to three business days until Your Personal  
Information is completely removed from all records.  
You can access, review and change most of Your Personal Information by logging on to WeArticles at  
any time. However, some of your Personal Information can only be changed by contacting our  
Customer Service at  admin@WeArticles.com. You are required to promptly update your  
Personal Information if changes occur or information is inaccurate.  
Your WeArticles account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected.  
Please note that You are not permitted to provide Your password to anyone else. WeArticles will never  
ask for Your password in e-mails that You receive unexpectedly or that You did not request.  
Please remember to log-out of Your account and to close Your internet browser window when  
You leave the WeArticles Website; this is especially important if you use a PC in a public location. At  
present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to Your Personal Information. We  
assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.  
WeArticles treats data as a valuable asset that must be safeguarded and protected. As set forth above,  
we use reasonable security measures to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized  
access and disclosure.  
12\. Member Conduct  
You understand that all information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics,  
video, messages or other materials (“Content”), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted,  
are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated. This means that  
You, and not WeArticles, are entirely responsible for all Content that You upload, post, or otherwise  
transmit. WeArticles does not control the Content posted and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy,  
integrity, or quality of such Content. You understand that by using the Website, You may be  
exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable.  
You agree to not use the Website in order to:  
upload, post, or otherwise transmit any Content that is unlawful, harmful,  
threatening, abusive, harassing, tortious, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous,  
invasive of another’s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise  
objectionable;  
harm minors in any way;  
impersonate any person or entity, including, but not limited to, a WeArticles official,  
forum leader, guide or host, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your  
affiliation with a person or entity;  
forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of  
any Content transmitted through the Website or develop restricted or password-  
only access pages, or hidden pages or images (those not linked to from another  
accessible page);  
upload, post, or otherwise transmit any Content that You do not have a right to  
transmit under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as  
inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed  
as part of employment relationships or under non-disclosure agreements);  
upload, post, or otherwise transmit any Content that infringes any patent,  
trademark, trade secret, copyright, or other proprietary rights of any party;  
upload, post, or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising,  
promotional materials, “junk mail,” “spam,” “chain letters,” “pyramid schemes,”  
or any other form of solicitation, except in those areas of the Website that are  
designated for such purpose;  
upload, post, or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or  
any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit  
the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications  
equipment;  
interfere with or disrupt the servers or networks connected to the Website,  
or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks  
connected to the site;  
intentionally or unintentionally violate any applicable local, state, national or  
international law, including, but not limited to, regulations promulgated by the  
U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, any rules of any national or other  
securities exchange, including, without limitation, the New York Stock Exchange,  
the American Stock Exchange or the NASDAQ, and any regulations having the  
force of law;  
stalk” or otherwise harass another;  
collect or store personal data about other users;  
promote or provide instructional information about illegal activities, promote  
physical harm or injury against any group or individual, or promote any act of  
cruelty to animals;  
use Your home page (or directory) as storage for remote loading or as a door or  
signpost to another home page; or  
engage in commercial activities without the express written consent of WeArticles.  
This includes, but is not limited to, the following activities: offering for sale any  
products or services, soliciting for advertisers or sponsors, conducting raffles or  
contests that require any type of entry fee, displaying a sponsorship banner of  
any kind, including those that are generated by banner or link exchange services,  
displaying banners for services that provide cash or cash-equivalent prizes to  
users in exchange for hyperlinks to their websites.  
13\. Rights  
You acknowledge that we acquire all Rights to use any posted materials as described above so  
that we do not violate any Rights You may have in materials You post. By submitting content  
to or through the Website, You grant us the non-exclusive right to reproduce, modify, and  
distribute it as we see fit in any medium and for any purpose in any form, media, or technology  
now known or later developed. You also permit any other user to access, display, and print such  
content for personal use. You vouch that any material you submit does not violate, plagiarize, or  
infringe upon the right of any third-party, including copyright, trademark, or proprietary rights.  
If non-original content is included in Your posting, You must obtain permission from the content  
owner and attribute it.  
14\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS  
A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third-parties for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third-parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.  
15\. Copyrights and Copyright Agent  
WeArticles respects the rights of all copyright holders. If You believe that Your work has been copied  
and used on our Website in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide WeArticles  
Copyright Agent the following information required by Section 512 of the Digital Millennium  
Copyright Act:  
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the  
owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;  
Identification of the copyright work claimed to have been infringed, or, if  
multiple copyrighted works at a single on-line site are covered by a single  
notification, a representative list of such works at that site;  
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject  
of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be  
disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;  
Information reasonably sufficient to contact the complaining party;  
A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the  
material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its  
agent, or the law; and  
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty  
of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner  
of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.  
WeArticles Copyright Agent may be contacted at: Copyright Agent, , Los Angeles,  
CA 90046.  
We appreciate the opportunity to serve You!  
WeArticles.com® owns and operates the WeArticles Website. You may  
contact us directly if you have any questions regarding the content and material on the Website  
or if you have any questions about our Privacy Policies. Please contact our Privacy Officer at:  
WeArticles® Los Angeles, CA 90046  
Additionally, You may contact your state or local consumer protection office, The Direct  
Marketing Association’s Committee on Ethical Business Practices, the Better Business Bureau,  
or The Federal Trade Commission by phone at (202) FTC-HELP (202/382-4357) and online at  
"http://www.ftc.gov" www.ftc.gov.  
Note: This Privacy Policy applies to WeArticles Website and to WeArticles’s other information gathering activities.  
WeArticles complies with all the stringent standards of ethical conduct set forth by the Direct  
Marketing Association.  
© 2013 WeArticles®. All Rights Reserved.
